<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="welcome_message_title">Welcome to Nook Helper!</string>
    <string name="welcome_message_body">We\'ll help you meticulously manage your AnimalCrossing life :)</string>
    <string name="start">Get Started</string>
    <string name="add_user_title">Add an Account</string>
    <string name="add_user_body">The information you enter can be changed at any time.</string>
    <string name="add">Add</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="name_placeholder">Lily, Tommy, …</string>
    <string name="island_name">Island Name</string>
    <string name="island_name_placeholder">Atlantis, Batcave, …</string>
    <string name="hemisphere">Hemisphere</string>
    <string name="north_hemisphere">North</string>
    <string name="south_hemisphere">South</string>
    <string name="progress_by_day">Day %d Progress</string>
    <string name="today_task">Today\'s Tasks</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="progress_card_description">You don\'t have to finish everything in one day. Feel free to take your time and enjoy!</string>
    <string name="move_to_next_day_description">Moving to day %d.\n(You can also move by pressing the arrow at the bottom.)</string>
    <string name="move_to_todo_description">Congratulations🎉 You have completed the tutorial!\n(Moving to the TODO app.)</string>

    <string name="tutorial_task_name1">Follow the NPC\'s instructions to progress through the tutorial</string>
    <string name="tutorial_task_detail_description1">The locations of your home and the villagers\' homes can be changed later.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_task_name2">Get a bed from Nook and install it in the tent to sleep</string>

    <string name="tutorial_task_name3">Donate 5 creatures and decide on the location for Blathers\' tent</string>
    <string name="tutorial_task_detail_description3">Later on, you\'ll donate all types of creatures to the museum, so feel free to donate any creature.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_task_name4">Wait until the next day</string>
    <string name="tutorial_task_detail_description4_1">Animal Crossing is a slow-life game that reflects real time, date, and seasons.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_task_detail_description4_2">From now on, sleeping in the bed won\'t skip to the next day. It has to be 5 AM in real time to move to the next day.</string>

    <string name="tutorial_task_name5">Get the shovel and vaulting pole recipes from Blathers\' tent</string>
    <string name="tutorial_task_detail_description5_1">Eating one piece of fruit allows you to completely remove a rock or tree.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_task_detail_description5_2">However, since rocks only spawn on the island at a rate of 1 per day, with a maximum of 6, and there are important items that only come from rocks, it\'s better not to break them.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_task_name6">Donate 15 creatures</string>
    <string name="tutorial_task_name7">Gather materials for the shop: 30 wood, 30 softwood, 30 hardwood, 30 iron nuggets</string>
    <string name="tutorial_task_detail_description7_1">Iron nuggets are precious items found only in rocks, making it hard to collect 30 in one day.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_task_detail_description7_2">[Tip 1]\nBy digging holes like in the picture and standing between the hole and the rock, you can get up to 8 items by quickly hitting the rocks.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_task_detail_description7_3">[Tip 2]\nYou can also visit a mystery island using a Nook Miles Ticket, purchasable for 2,000 Nook Miles at the Nook Stop.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_task_detail_description7_4">[Tip 3]\nHow to visit a mystery island: Go to the airport -> Talk to Orville -> Select "visit other places." -> Use a Nook Miles Ticket\n(Since a NMT can be sold for more than 100K bells online, use them wisely!)</string>

    <string name="tutorial_task_name8">Choose spots for villagers’ houses and get the ladder recipe</string>
    <string name="tutorial_task_name9">Build a bridge</string>
    <string name="tutorial_task_name10">Fill empty house plots with furniture</string>
    <string name="tutorial_task_detail_description10_1">As soon as you fill an empty house plot with furniture, a villager to move in is randomly determined. However, you can use NMTs to bring in a specific villager you want.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_task_detail_description10_2">[How to get villager you want]\n1. Before filling the house plot with furniture, visit a mystery islands many times until you find a villager you like.\n2. Invite the villager to your island.\n3. Fill the house plot with furniture.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_task_detail_description10_3">[Caution]\nVillagers will appear on a mystery island only if there is an unclaimed empty house plot. If the plot is marked \'SOLD\' in red letters, a villager has already been determined.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_task_detail_description10_4">Besides NMT, the campsite and amiibo are methods to fill your island with desired villagers.</string>
</resources>